ELIJAH DANKO

Senior Software Engineer



+48-538-941-416 elijahdanko.net



elijahdanko



PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Overall, nine years of working experience in the field. Have participated in various technologies and programming languages, including C, C++, Java, Clojure, Javascript, and Python. Started as a system engineer and was moving to the Web, and Golang, in particular. I'm strongly focused on business' needs, and as a Free Software user, considering contributing further back to Open Source.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer

Aigent

Dec 2019 - Ongoing

Amsterdam, NL

- Troubleshooting high performing components.
- Design, develop and maintain services and internal tools.
- · Refine existing parts.
- · Collaboration with clients.

Senior Software Engineer

Omnisend

Feb 2018 - Dec 2019

Lviv, UA

- Design, develop and maintain high performing services.
- Write unit, acceptance and e2e tests.

Senior Test Engineer

Here

Jun 2017 - Feb 2018

Lviv, UA

- Design and develop integration testing framework.
- Implement and maintain integration tests.

Middle Software Engineer

Cisco

■ Nov 2015 - Jun 2017

Lviv, UA

- Develop and maintain gateway systems for embedded devices.
- Develop and maintain primitive components and drivers, such as, VOIP, IPTV, VPN.
- Write user guides and other technical documentations.
- Maintain and extend the testing framework solution with tests.

Junior Software Engineer

Inside Secure

Jul 2013 - Nov 2015

Lviv, UA

- Develop and maintain a stereotyped simulator for credit card vendors.
- Write and maintain integration tests.

TECH STACK

General Purpose Languages

Golang C Javascript Clojure Python C++ Java

Domain Specific Languages

Bash Makefile CMake Javascript SQL family MongoDB ELisp Lua Elm La Html Sass & Css
React Protobuf

LANGUAGES

English

Ukrainian

Ukrainian

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Economics

Volodymyr Dahl East Ukrainian National University

Sep 2010 - Jun 2013